quick announcement that I'm super
excited for. This Sunday, October 26th,
at 11:00 a.m. Central time, I'm doing my
first ever live AI agent build as a live
stream. All my other streams in the past
have been more focused on Q&A. I did
something kind of similar with NAND in
the past, but this is the real deal.
Building a complete AI agent and using
AI coding assistance. And if you're
watching this after the stream already
happened, no worries. I'll have a link
to the recording in the description. And
not only will I be showing you how to
use AI coding assistance to build any AI
agent, I also have an awesome use case
for our stream. I teased recently that
I'm working on this AI agent that I'll
be showing how I build on my YouTube
channel. It's your own personal AI
coach. So, it's an AI agent with a lot
of advanced rag techniques that's
trained on all of my YouTube content. I
want to extend that to more than just
YouTube later as well. And so it's a
really practical agent to be a resource
alongside all of my YouTube content. And
we're going to be building this from the
ground up together, which I'm just so
excited for. So link in the description
to the live stream. Go over there,
enable notifications for it. Again,
that's this Sunday, the 26th, at 11:00
a.m. Central time. Building our personal
AI coach for both AI agents and AI
coding assistants because that's what I
cover on my channel. And this is going
to be trained on my YouTube content to
start. And then I want to expand the
knowledge base over time to include
other sources as well. So I got big
plans for this agent, but I want to
build it with you live. I think that's
going to be so exciting. And so there
are four core technologies that we're
going to be focusing on in the live
stream. So just giving you a little bit
of a teaser for what's coming as we
build this together. And so starting
with YouTube, this is obviously going to
be the primary data source for our rag
pipeline. So, we'll build a simple yet
effective rag pipeline together for
ingesting YouTube videos and we'll
include the extraction of metadata and
timestamps. Like, it's not going to be
extremely trivial and we're going to do
that so we can have more advanced rag
tools that I'll talk about in a sec. And
this is going to work for any YouTube
channel. So, theoretically, this agent
that I build, you could turn it into an
expert for really any content creator.
Pretty cool. And for the AI agent
framework, we're going to obviously be
building in Python. That's what I always
cover on my channel. And Pyantic AI is
still my favorite AI agent framework and
it has been for quite a while. And we'll
be giving our Pyantic AI agent a few
different rag tools to query YouTube
videos. And I'm going to make it so that
it's going to work for really any large
language model. So we'll be able to use
Open Router, Olama, Anthropic, OpenAI,
all these different providers. I want to
be very LLM agnostic and I'll be
focusing a lot on the tools that I give
to the agent because I want to apply
some more advanced rag strategies to
make that a really practical part of the
stream as well. So applying different
strategies for ultra accurate retrieval
and even giving the agent to pull
transcripts if it needs. So it's more
like an agentic rag solution where the
agent gets to reason about how it
searches through the YouTube transcripts
and we'll have token streaming with a
complete front end. like this is going
to be a full stack application that I've
got in store for you. And speaking of
full stack, for our database, we will be
using a superbase. And so this will be
where we store all of our YouTube
videos, including the transcripts and
the embeddings that we have for rag and
then metadata as well for more advanced
rag techniques. being able to do
metadata filtering and things like that
to make sure that our rag solution can
be very precise and then authentication
for our front-end application because I
do want to make this something that is
deployed to the cloud ready for you,
anyone viewing my YouTube videos to
leverage at some point. And so obviously
you'll need authentication for that. And
then last but not least, something I
covered pretty recently on my channel is
a tool for rag called Dockling. And this
is especially useful for the hybrid
chunking that they have available. So,
more on this when we build with Dockling
together in a couple of days here. But
this chunking strategy is actually going
to be super critical for accurate rag
for a YouTube transcript. So, we'll be
using Dockling for that local models so
everything is blazing fast and later I
can extend this to support uploading
PDFs for when I expand the different
sources for the knowledge base. So,
that's everything going into this agent.
So, it's going to be super practical,
super hands-on. It's going to be pretty
casual and engaging as well, like I
always like to make my live streams.
It's going to be a blast. And the goal
that I have for you, the primary goal is
to give you a super straightforward
example of building a pretty practical
AI agent. I hope this seems really
practical to you and it's going to be
using a full AI coding assistant
workflow. So, of course, we're going to
be using AI coding assistants. I'll use
claude code in the stream, but I'll talk
about how this will work with really any
AI coding assistant. And then for task
management and rag, we're going to use
the good old archon because this is my
open source tool that I have available
for you to enhance any AI coding
workflow. So of course, I wouldn't miss
including it in everything that we've
got right now. And by the way, a massive
reason that I'm doing this live stream
is cuz I want to celebrate the release
of the Agentic coding course in Dynamis.
So, I'll have a link to this in the
description as well, so you can check it
out because if you want to master AI
coding assistance and learn how to build
reliable, repeatable systems that get
you results you didn't even know was
possible with AI coding assistance. This
is for you. I promise you're not going
to find anything better. And you got to
understand, I have to tell you about
this right now because the first batch
of the course was released right into
the Dynamis community literally today.
So, it's on the forefront of my mind.
I'm super excited for this. We're going
to be releasing the course in batches to
the community over the next month and
having live workshops to go along with
these releases. So, it's going to be
super engaging. I just released the
module about the core mental models of
AI coding and principles. Then, we'll
get into building your own system that
is optimized for your use case and your
code bases. And then getting into how
you can automate your workflows,
integrate with your applications. We'll
even get into more advanced things like
remote AI coding. And then finally
getting into some more out-of-the-box
solutions that you can leverage and
learn from to build your systems like
the PRP framework, the BMAD method, and
the GitHub spec kit. So really covering
the full landscape for AI coding and
taking your systems to a level that is
just probably unimaginable for you right
now. And the core mental model that I
cover here is that every mistake is an
opportunity to evolve your system. So
when AI screws up something in your
code, instead of just fixing it
yourself, you fix your system and retry.
And when you iterate on this over and
over again, you end up with this system
that is perfectly crafted for you. And
that really is your competitive
advantage. So definitely check out the
Dynamus Aentic coding course. But with
that, back to the main announcement for
this video for the live stream. Again,
that is this Sunday, the 26th, at 11:00
a.m. Central time. It's going to be
super practical, super fun, and we're
building something that's going to be an
incredible resource for the channel
going forward. And so with that, I will
see you this Sunday for the first ever
live agent